pmease.com 2015-04-28

# PMEase - Legal - Continuous integration and deployment solution!

We at PMEase Inc. ("PMEase" or "we") respect your individual privacy. This privacy policy documents our adherence to the highest industry standards for the protection of your personal information. The policy is effective as of July 1, 2008, applies to the site pmease.com and any other web sites of PMEase Software. 

## Why we collect personal information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. 

If you do not want PMEase to keep you up to date with PMEase news, software updates and the latest information on products and services click [ www.pmease.com/account](http://www.pmease.com/account) and update your personal contact information and preferences. 

## What information we collect and how we may use it

PMEase is the sole owner of the information collected on the site. PMEase may collect information at several different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information from all visitors to the site. This type of information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of our site. Second, we require the submission of certain personally identifiable information (name and e-mail address) when you sign up for a user account. Registration allows you to activate/extend your QuickBuild service, generate your site licenses and otherwise access a broader range of online resources. The same items of personal information are required if you subscribe to receive our newsletter, or if you send an e-mail inquiry to our customer service department. 

## How we protect your personal information

PMEase takes precautions including administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

PMEase does not sell, rent or share customer information with any third party not affiliated with or owned by PMEase, except service providers who assist PMEase in such areas as data storage or direct mailing. PMEase will never give or sell your personal information to be used for the purposes of sending you unsolicited commercial offers (such as spam) from any third party. We may send you infrequent e-mail notices regarding PMEase products or services that may be of interest to you. You may choose not to receive these notices. 

To make purchases from the PMEase, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Firefox, Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it transmitted over the Internet. 

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Firefox, Safari. 

If you have any questions about the security at pmease.com, you can [send a message](http://www.pmease.com/contact) to Customer Service. 

## Integrity of your personal information

PMEase has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by checking at [www.pmease.com/account](http://www.pmease.com/account). And you can request a copy of your personal information, your product registration history, and your interactions with our sales and support agents by [sending a message](http://www.pmease.com/contact) to us. 

## Cookies and other technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, PMEase uses cookies and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services, such as QuickBuild. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us. 

The cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Allowing the pmease.com cookie to remain on your computer makes it easier for you to log in to and use the site. If you reject the cookie, you may still use the site, but you will be required to verify your identity at various points. 

## Our companywide commitment to your privacy

As we said, PMEase takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to PMEase employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. 

## Privacy questions

If you have questions or concerns about our Online Privacy Policy or data processing, please use the email addresses below to contact us. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days. 

If you do not want PMEase to keep you up to date with PMEase news, software updates and the latest information on products and services click [www.pmease.com/account](http://www.pmease.com/account) and update your personal contact information and preferences. Naturally, if you notify us that you do not want us to use your information for a particular purpose, we will not do so. 

PMEase reserves the right to change its privacy policy from time to time. Please refer to this site periodically for any changes. 

_Last updated January 18, 2009_  
_© 2007 PMEase Inc. All rights reserved._
